

# Anastasiia Pyslar

Junior Software Engineer

■ pyslar.anastasiia@gmail.com 

→ +38 (066)-546-03-33 

◆ Lviv, Ukraine

## **Profesional Summary**

Have experience in developing desktop software, web applications and servers using node.is, .net, aolana and react/anaular, Futhermore, have experience in team working within different type of projects. Solid understanding of OOP, SOLID, patterns, REST and networking. Skilled team player with strong background. Works well independently to handle assignments and always ready to go beyond basics tasks. Quick learner and hard-working. Easy going when it comes to get along with co-workers.

### Education

#### Software Engineering

Lviv Polytechnic National University, Lviv

Sep 2020 - Jun 2024

I have learned foundational programming concepts, software design principles, algorithms, and various programming languages. Additionally, I delved into topics such as software development methodologies, version control systems, database management, system architecture, and possibly gained exposure to emerging technologies. Moreover, my time at university enhanced many soft skills.

Jun 2023 **NET Intership** 

Eleks University, Lviv

During the internship working on the team project "City Ride," I learned to implement various technologies like Kafka, RabbitMQ, and Microservice architecture. I gained hands-on experience in collaborative development, focusing on building a scalable and efficient system.

# **Employment**

Basic .Net Mar 2022 - May 2022

Sigma Software, Lviv Ukraine

Have mastered the basics of the language .Net, took part in product development during the whole course, and have consolidated knowledge on the use of software development patterns and SOLID principles.

.Net Marathon Feb 2022 - May 2022

Softserve, Lviv Ukarine

Mastered the upper level of the language C#, practiced while working in the team and practiced in distributing ASP.NET and UML diagrams tried myself in the role of QA, Front and Back Developer.

Hackaton Sep 2021 - Sep 2021

Institute of computer Science and Information Technologies, Lviv Ukraine

During three weeks the game in the team was developed, where I was art-designer and developer of different mechanics of the game. The project was executed in the language C# in the environment Unity.

## **Hobbies**

Reading ■ Gym

Painting ■ Self-learning Personal details

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/anastasia-pyslar

github.com/nastiiiii

Skills

C# (.Net, ASP.NET)

OOP, SOLID, Data Types and structures

Html5/CSS3

Javascript

**Entity Framework** 

Patterns

SQL (MSSQL, PostgresSql)

React/Angular

Golang

C++

Languages

Ukranian

English

German